I: What do you usually do in the evening after school?
S: Um, I usually go to sports practices, and finish homework,
and have dinner and things.
I: What kind of films do you like?
S: Normally action movies or comedy.
I: Do you usually watch films at home or at the cinema?
S: Depends.
If it’s a good action movie, I like to go out and watch.
I: When’s your birthday?
S: My birthday is the fifth of April.
I: What do you usually do on your birthday?
S: Go out for a meal with family and friends.
I: Do you drive to work?
K: Yes, I do.
I: Can you park near where you work?
K: Yes, there’s a car park at my office.
I: What do you like doing at the weekend?
R: Er, I like cycling, walking, um, socializing, cooking.